Guide to the Thomas E. Dixon Papers, 1967-1993
Duke University. University Archives
- Accession A94-31, 1967-1993, (19 boxes)
  - Auxiliary Services Report to the Advisory Committee on Resources, 1989 (Box 18)
  - Human Resources, 1983-1984 (Box 18)
  - Job Enhancement Program, 1984-1986, (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Job Enhancement Program--retreat, 1985-1986 (Box 18)
  - Job Enhancement Program--training, 1983-1984, (4 folders) (Box 18)
  - Bus accident: Report on the Bus Accident to President H. Keith H. Brodie, Safety Task Force, 1993 Feb. 1 (Box 18)
    [Restricted until 2018.]
  - East Campus Task Force, 1992 (Box 18)
  - Buildings and grounds, 1990 (Box 18)
  - Tel-Com Advisory Committee--current agenda, 1990-1991, (4 folders) (Box 18)
  - Troika, 1986-1991, (4 folders) (Box 18)
    "Troika" was the name for a three-person committee appointed by President H. Keith H. Brodie in 1986 to review recommendations for space allocation and capital acquisitions. In addition to correspondence, notes, and minutes, files also contain blueprints.